- Hey.
- Morning.
- Coffee?
- Thank you.
- Made you breakfast.
- Oh, you shouldn't have.
Well, when there's a guest,
I like to make a fuss.
- And I like the fuss you make.
- Yeah?
- Something wrong?
- Just... Work stuff.
Listen, I was wondering
if we could get dinner tonight.
Or... Is that weird because
we went out last night?
- Is... is two nights in a row weird?
- No. I don't think it's weird.
Okay, good.
I'll make a reservation.
- A reservation, huh?
- Like I said, I like to make a fuss.
I have to go to work.
I will take this to go.
- I'll see you later?
- Yeah.
- Morning, Lisbon.
- Hey, Jane.
Hey. We just got a call
from the forest service.
They caught a body
in Sam Houston national forest.
Abbott wants you guys
to go check it out.
- How far away is that?
- 100, 120 miles.
- Is there a problem?
- No. No.
She has plans for tonight.
She's worried about getting back in time.
- Really?
- Actually, it is not a problem.
Nonsense. Doesn't the FBI have helicopters?
Can't we just take one of those?
- I guess, if it's available.
- That will not be necessary.
Nonsense. We'll be up and back in a jiffy.
Just tell your agent Pike
he owes me a favor.
Hello, there!
Officer Green! Forestry service!
Thank you so much for coming!
This way!
Two hikers found her
around 9:00 this morning.
- Any identification?
- Nah. She's a Jane Doe.
But we did find this cellphone
about 10 feet from her body.
Must have fallen out of her pocket.
It's pretty beat-up.
Any idea how she died?
Well, medical examiner says
it must be a broken neck
somewhere between
6:00 and 8:00 this morning.
My first thought was maybe she was
hiking on the road above and fell
but... I don't know.
Something just seems off
about the body.
That's why I gave you guys a call.
- Sure hope I haven't wasted your time.
- Not at all, ranger Green.
In fact, you're very astute.
She wasn't hiking.
You know, you go hiking,
you wear some socks.
No socks...
and no blisters, either
so I don't think
she walked here.
New, off-brand sneakers and jeans.
Full face of makeup.
Expensive ginger-and-citrus shampoo.
She's a girl of slender means
going out to meet someone
she wanted to look good for.
Any idea where she could have
been brought from?
There's nothing around here
for miles, except the club.
- Club?
- Yeah
the Foragers' club.
It's just up the road.
It's kind of a ritzy place.
Very exclusive... men only.
But, nah, she didn't come from there.
- Now, how do you know that?
- Well, I called as soon as we found her.
All their female employees
are accounted for.
And, like I said,
they don't allow female guests.
No one's missing.
"Morning. Welcome to the Foragers' club.
How may I help you?"
- We're with the FBI. Let us in, please.
- "What's this about?"
One of your members
murdered somebody.
"We'd like to talk to someone
about that."
- I need to talk to someone at...
- "Hello?"
Mr. Jane. Agent Lisbon.
Welcome to the Foragers'.
I'm Kenyon Russell.
I'm the president.
Listen, before we begin
I need to ask you to wear one of these
while you're on the grounds.
All the staff and guests wear them.
Just, one of those rules.
- All men, huh?
- Yeah.
- What's that about?
- Well, it's just simple brotherhood, ma'am.
We're not anti-female...
not at all.
We're fully chartered
by the state of Texas
as a private,
single-sex organization.
We have, uh, female employees...
mainly in the dining hall.
But, uh, we just don't accept
women for membership.
- Are women allowed as guests?
- Generally no
though there have been exceptions...
First ladies, for instance.
But none recently.
Please... sit.
I know this all sounds very old-school
but you have to understand...
Our members are senators, judges, C.E.O.s
They're successful, driven men.
They really have very few places
that they can completely relax.
Here, we have no cellphones, no twitter
no distractions from the outside world.
- Women are a distraction?
- Well, no, of course not.
But we offer, um, um...
very... unique kind of camaraderie.
The Foragers' is a...
It's a very special place for a lot of us
a place our fathers and grandfathers built
and brought us to.
Then how did our Jane Doe
get on the property?
She wasn't on our property.
If she was, I'd know. We have excellent
security systems in place.
Do you know this woman?
This is the poor woman
who died, I assume.
No, I don't recognize her.
Oh, that's kind of weird,
'cause she was killed here.
And if she were here,
then you would know, right?
That's a very serious
accusation, Mr. Jane.
- I hope you...
- The victim was found
with two holes in her shirt right here...
Made from a pin like this.
So she was wearing
one of these badges...
Like this.
She was killed here, and she
was dumped outside the gate.
Holes in her shirt? That's a pretty,
tenuous theory, at best.
Tenuous?
We are 50 miles from nowhere
and that poor woman is dead
outside your gate.
Tenuous, it is not, sir.
Now, I hope we can rely
on your full cooperation.
Yes, ma'am.
I can't promise
she won't hurt anyone.
I'll try to restrain her,
but I can't promise.
Sorry.
How many people
are on the grounds?
182 campers and 97 staff.
There'll be more people
coming for the talk tomorrow.
- The talk?
- Yeah
we have a speaker
coming in from Silicon Valley
to speak about digital technology
and the economy.
We're gonna need the names of everybody
who was here last night.
Well, our membership list
is confidential. You...
- I can get a subpoena, if I have to.
- That won't be necessary.
I was merely gonna counsel you
to... exercise discretion here
for your own sake.
Our members are... Powerful people.
You can see our concierge,
Peter Kilgallen
and he'll give you
the information you need.
His office is right down there
and to the right.
- Thank you.
- Give it back!
- Hey! Hey, give that b...
- Mr. Russell...
- Don't treat me like a child!
- Mr. Russell.
I'm sorry. I found Mr. Gryska
using his cellphone.
Marvin.
- What are you gonna do? Spank me?
- You know the rule.
- There's no cellphones on the grounds.
- I was talking to my lawyer.
- I have matters that need attention.
- Okay, all right, Marvin
if you have business to do you're welcome
to take care of it off the grounds, please.
- Oh, forget it. Who are you?
- Teresa Lisbon, FBI.
Oh, here about
the dead girl, huh?
That's great. First woman here in
a hundred years... she's a fed.
- Excuse me.
- Charmer.
Marvin Gryska is one of our,
newer members.
I'll let Kilgallen know
you're coming.
- Good luck with the investigation.
- Thank you.
I think you can deal
with Kilgallen.
- I'm gonna take a walk.
- What for?
- Men stuff.
- Men stuff? Okay.
Any luck identifying
our forest victim?
We didn't get any matches
off fingerprints.
Facial recognition
didn't pull up any names, either.
What about the cellphone they found?
Techs are still working on it
but haven't dug anything out yet.
Hey. Spoke to the manager
of a motel in the area.
He said a woman matching
our victim's description
checked in yesterday morning
but according to housekeeping,
she hadn't slept in her room.
He faxed me a copy
of her driver's license.
That's her.
Madison Pryce. Austin address.
I tried calling her apartment.
Nobody answered.
I spoke to the super
in the building.
He said Pryce's younger sister's
been staying with her.
- I'll bring her in.
- All right. Let Lisbon and Jane know.
- Mr. Kilgallen?
- Oh, you must be agent Lisbon, right?
- Yeah.
- Yeah. Here you go.
The names and contact numbers
of all the staff.
Also, all the members
that were here last night as of 7:00.
That's when we close the gates.
Keep that to yourself, though.
It's highly confidential.
I heard.
Does the name Madison Pryce
mean anything to you?
Madison Pryce... No. No.
Everyone heard about the woman
who died, though. Is that her name?
- You're certain she wasn't on staff here?
- Oh, yeah. Absolutely.
No one by that name's worked here
since I started
and that's about...
that's about five years now.
- What do you do exactly?
- Provide things for the campers...
Anything from a 120-year-old bottle
of brandy to a snakebite kit.
You wouldn't believe some of the stuff
I've had to track down.
I'll bet.
Listen, I don't mean to tell you
your business.
But I think you're barking up
the wrong tree.
- That woman... Madison Pryce, was it?
- Yeah.
- Yeah. She has nothing to do with us.
- Your boss, Russell, said the same thing.
Maybe we're right, then.
Alan. Alan!
Stop telling me to be realistic.
Just tell me how this ends well
for me, 'cause I...
I got to go.
- I won't narc. Don't worry.
- Thanks.
Use your phone, they make you
assume the position.
You were with that woman.
You're FBI.
- "With," not "of."
- Yeah, well, back up, g-man.
- I got nothing to say to you vultures.
- You've met the feds before now, I take it.
- Oh, you don't read the financial pages?
- Life's too short.
Your guys are
throwing the book at me.
Conspiracy to commit
securities fraud, wire fraud
bank fraud,
false S.E.C. filing.
And your lawyer's trying to convince you
to make a deal.
- Yeah... the schmuck.
- Will you?
- The hell I will.
- Bravo.
Quick question... Russell said
most of the women on staff
work in the dining hall.
You ever see them anyplace else?
No... just a bunch of fat guys with pleated
shorts as far as the eye can see.
That's a vivid image.
Okay, well, good luck with the FBI.
You know, they had me dead to rights
and I beat 'em. I think you can, too.
- What charge?
- Murder.
- How'd you do that?
- Got to know the right people.
Our mom and dad were killed
in a car accident when we were little.
The two of us spent years
in and out of foster homes.
And one night, Madison...
It was, it was "Margaret" then...
She ran away and I didn't hear
from her for months.
Then, on my birthday,
she sent me $50.
The next year she was paying for me
to go to boarding school.
When I graduated, I asked her
if I could stay with her for a little while.
- Where did the money come from?
- She worked.
As a temp, at first and then
she started her own company.
It helps executives
with their speaking skills.
She e-mailed me this morning.
"Dee, gentle reminder...
Fish must eat, or fish will die."
- "Love you."
- She's in a cabin.
Could someone have snuck her into
the Foragers' camp, a boyfriend, maybe?
Madison didn't have any boyfriends.
She was gay.
- Any girlfriends?
- Not serious ones.
She worked too hard.
Their business wasn't doing well.
Do you have any idea why she might
have been at the Foragers' club?
No. She never mentioned it.
We can talk to the waitstaff
after they're done with lunch service.
According to the maître d',
it should be an hour and a half.
Not to worry.
Excuse me? Miss?
Could you pour my friend
some coffee, please? Thank you.
- Tell Pike I say hi.
- How do you know it's Pike?
"Jane says hi."
- Yeah, he seems like a good guy.
- He is.
Good, 'cause you deserve to be
with a good man.
Thanks.
Excuse me, ma'am.
I'd like to get some cream.
Thank you.
Excuse me. This... This fork is dirty.
There. You see that?
- How about this one?
- Oh, yeah, that's clean. Thank you.
Nice and clean. Excellent.
- Okay. What is going on?
- The video Madison Pryce made
showed that she stayed in a cabin
the night before she died.
She was gay, so it was unlikely
a man's cabin...
More likely a friend or a lover.
She washed her hair
so she probably borrowed the shampoo
from the other woman.
None of these women here
used that shampoo.
But by process of elimination, it leaves...
Excuse me, miss.
Yes, ma'am, you.
Come here, please.
Ginger citrus. Very nice.
Very nice.
There we are.
You were with Madison Pryce last night.
- Excuse me?
- Do you know Madison Pryce, ma'am?
Oh, my God.
It's her, isn't it?
She's the murdered woman.
Oh, my God.
And when was the last time
that you saw Madison?
This morning.
A little after 5:00...
that's when she left my cabin.
We weren't a couple.
I mean, we hooked up
when she came to the camp
but it wasn't serious.
We just... Liked each other.
- How did you meet?
- Last year...
A late-night beer party for staff.
She just roamed in.
I had no idea where she'd come from.
- What was she doing there?
- Work.
It was a gig for her.
What kind of gig?
- She was an escort.
- A... prostitute?
She preferred "escort."
She kept it quiet
so her sister wouldn't find out.
The public-speaking business
was a cover story.
- She was gay.
- It helped.
She didn't take men
too seriously.
- So, she was at the club to meet a client?
- Yeah, at the Fishing Camp.
Fishing Camp?
Okay.
Thank you.
That was Fischer.
According to Pam Madison Pryce
worked as a prostitute
at a brothel they maintain on the grounds
called the Fishing Camp.
So you run a brothel at the Foragers.
The club provides a service...
at not one I avail myself of.
Sure. And it's called...
Fishing Camp.
In my father's and grandfather's time
it actually was, used for fishing.
- But not anymore.
- We had a problem.
In years past people would go to a house
about 20 miles away from the camp
when they... wanted
that kind of thing.
But there was drunkenness,
accidents, arrests.
Not a healthy situation
in the age of the camera phone.
So Kilgallen...
came up with the idea of moving
the enterprise onto our grounds
as a way of avoiding the difficulties.
And it worked.
- We've had no problems since then.
- Except a murder.
Yes. Obviously.
- So, it was Kilgallen's operation?
- Yeah. Completely.
He brings the women up on the weekends
usually one or two at a time.
Got them on some sort of rotation.
The Foragers', by the way,
derives no income from this.
I was very firm about that.
- Did you know Madison Pryce?
- No.
According to Pam Parsons
Madison visited the camp several times.
- You never saw her?
- Well, that wasn't your question.
You asked me if I knew her, which I did not
by any reasonable definition of the term.
Upon reconsideration, I think it's possible
that I did see her once or twice.
We never spoke.
Now, you told Jane
you didn't recognize her picture.
Not many people can get an evasion
like that past Jane.
- Your point being...
- You must be a very good liar.
Where were you from 6:00 to 8:00
this morning?
I was asleep.
Whoo!
Hey! Look who I found.
- What are you doing here?
- Well, you have poked the bear.
After Russell was questioned
he called a few high-powered people,
and they called me
so I figured I'd come down
and check everything out.
- Where's Kilgallen?
- I don't know. He's not in his office.
His laptop isn't there, either.
Camp security is looking for him.
He's on the run.
Not the type to pack a bag.
All right. Well, I'll have Fischer
start a search.
- So, this is the Fishing Camp, huh?
- Madison used cabin 9.
Pam Parsons says that Madison left her
cabin at 5:00 this morning to come here.
That was the last time
anybody saw her.
- I don't think she died here.
- What makes you say that?
Well, there's nothing out of place.
There's no scratches on the floor
from furniture sliding.
A fight would have left marks.
Well, I would have called it just a hunch,
but that works, too.
Maybe it started in here
and then went outside.
Either way, the killer had to have used
something to move the body.
There's no way they carried it
to where it was found.
There are a lot of golf carts here.
Get forensics up here.
Have them test the golf carts.
Tell them to bring the m-vac system.
That'll dig DNA fragments out of anything.
And if Madison's DNA is on that golf cart
then the killer's might be, too.
What is that?
Wait a minute.
It's a golf-ball marker.
You use it to, uh,
place your ball on the Green.
whoever visited this room
must've been a serious linksman.
But a place like this, ah,
that must be a lot of people.
I think we can narrow it down.
Grant Kimura.
Dennis Abbott, FBI.
I'm a fan. I saw you play
in Augusta last summer.
That putt that you made
on the seventh...
- Oh, that was amazing.
- Amazing.
Patrick Jane.
I don't know anything about golf.
Okay. Cool.
What's this about?
All security told me was some guys
from the FBI wanted to talk.
I got a massage in 15.
Well, we found something
that belongs to you.
- Where'd you get that?
- Over at the Fishing Camp.
You know it, don't you?
Sure you do.
No, man. I don't know
what you're talking about.
- Plays golf better than he lies, huh?
- Who are you, again?
We found it in a cabin that is used
by a woman named Madison Pryce.
It must have just fallen out of your pocket
while you were there.
There are a million of those.
Could belong to anyone.
Yeah, well, the Fishing Camp's
for a certain kind of man...
Pampered, hedonistic, self-centered.
Certainly screams out "professional athlete."
Now, we're talking to a lot of people
about the Fishing Camp.
If you deny being there
and we find out that you lied
that's obstruction of justice.
It's worth thinking about.
I'm married, okay?
Two little boys. And my endorsements
they require a certain... Public image.
Oh, we get it. We get it.
You're in a tough place.
Grant, what's going on?
- Are these people hassling you?
- Man, Greg, thanks for coming.
I heard from a security guy the FBI
wanted to talk to you.
You guys are FBI, right?
Well, I'm Gregory Dyer.
I'm Mr. Kimura's Attorney.
So whatever conversation or interrogation
you have going on here is over
because he's not
gonna say anything.
And the idea
that you would question him
without an attorney present
is a shocking professional lapse.
- I'll be complaining to your superiors.
- So frisky.
Oh, we were just talking to Mr. Kimura
about a woman named Madison Pryce
who was killed earlier this morning.
Now, we believe Mr. Kimura saw Ms. Pryce
within the last 24 hours.
So anything that he saw or heard
that would be a great help
to finding her killer
which we assume
he wants us to do.
- Nice try.
- Okay, Abbott, let's go.
It's obvious we're no match
for the keen legal mind of Mr. Dyer here.
You're not actually a member
of the Foragers', are you?
No, I'm here as grant's guest.
Yeah, I didn't think so.
You're too, sweaty.
Why don't you have one
of those guest-badge thingies?
I'm what's called a residential guest.
We don't do that.
So concerned about status here,
aren't they?
By the way, your collar is frayed.
You might want to bill him
for a new shirt.
Still no sign of Kilgallen.
Fischer's put out a bolo.
Call the office. Get as many agents up
here as we can find to sweep the woods.
We got to find this guy.
How's it going with the golf cart?
The techs are working on it now.
One of the carts
was methodically cleaned...
No fingerprints, no dust. They don't
think they'll find any DNA, either.
Well, that's the death cart.
The weird thing is, the techs say that
the cart was washed within the last hour.
It's still wet.
- Why would the killer wait until now?
- That does seem odd.
All right. Well, ask around. See if anyone
saw who cleaned the golf cart.
Sure.
- Excuse me. Are you Abbott?
- Marvin. Marvin Gryska.
This is a... this is
a very energetic Forager.
You are Abbott with the FBI, right?
- Yes, I am supervisory agent Dennis Abbott.
- Okay. I need to talk to you.
- I'm busy.
- Have fun.
Just a minute of your time. Please.
Okay, what can I do for you?
I made a couple of calls.
That guy Jane who was just here...
He told me he beat a murder charge
the FBI had on him.
You're the agent that made
that deal for him, aren't you?
I don't know where you get your
information from, Mr. Gryska
- but I can't discuss that with you.
- It's okay. My information's good.
You're in Austin.
You have an agent there
named Matthews.
Jim Matthews
is in a different division.
Mr. Gryska,
I can't help you.
You just asked
what could you do for me.
That was a figure of speech.
I just heard your agent Matthews
has frozen my assets.
He's locked my money away.
And why?
Apparently, he thinks I'm a flight risk.
- Are you?
- No!
Because the case against me
is gonna collapse.
What was my crime?
I made money. I got rich.
And I made other people rich...
And not blue-chip types,
like these guys.
Teachers, firemen, cops...
people just like you.
What's your point?
Matthews is being unreasonable.
I'm looking for someone reasonable
from the FBI to mediate my situation
and I'd be very grateful
if I could find that person.
- So you're offering me a bribe?
- Well, no, no. No. That would be illegal.
I'm just looking to put
this mess behind me
so I can get back to the business
of making people rich.
- Can we discuss that, agent Abbott?
- I'll get back to you.
Okay. Great.
Soon.
But great.
I came looking for you but they said
you're still in the woods. I'm disappointed.
I'm sorry. I don't know
when I'm gonna be back.
Could we do dinner
tomorrow night, maybe?
No problem. What's holding you up?
This guy named Kilgallen took off.
He's nowhere to be found at the camp.
We put a bolo out on him,
but that didn't turn anything up.
We figure he rabbited into the woods.
It's gonna be dark in an hour
and there is no way
we're gonna find him at night.
Have your people tried accessing
a forestry satellite?
They're imaging that area all the time
looking for fire outbreaks.
That is an excellent idea.
I used one once to find a guy who was running
with some stolen Frederic Remingtons.
Check you out...
good-looking and helpful.
- Bye.
- "Bye."
We're at the map coordinates
you gave us.
Okay, according to the satellite image
there should be a clearing ahead.
Yeah, looks like there's something there.
Is it maybe a... a service vehicle?
All right. Got it.
- That our guy?
- Yeah. That's Kilgallen.
The techs and M.E. are
finishing up at the crime scene.
The gun that Kilgallen was shot with
appears to have been taken
from the club's trapshooting range
but there's no prints on it.
- Any sign of Kilgallen's laptop?
- None. The killer must have taken it.
Well, it seems pretty clear
that Kilgallen was murdered
because he knew
who Madison Pryce's killer is.
So, tomorrow, we go at the club members
about Kilgallen, right?
Does anyone at the camp
know he's dead?
No, not yet.
- I wouldn't be too quick to mention it.
- Why not?
One dead body
makes people antsy.
They hear about Kilgallen,
the place will be empty by dinner.
- So what do we do?
- Good question.
Well, I'll let you people think about that.
I got to draft a memo to I.A.
Internal affairs?
What's going on with them?
Marvin Gryska all but offered me a bribe
to release his frozen assets.
- Oh, yeah?
- Well, he's desperate.
He's looking at 20 years.
Probably why he wants me
to release his assets...
So he can
run across the border.
- What'd you tell him?
- What I was supposed to tell him...
That I'll think about it.
And then I'll get him
to make that offer on tape
and we'll nail that fool's ass
for attempting to bribe a federal official.
Or you could not do any of that.
Why? Because I have a better plan.
Were we able to get anything
out of Madison Pryce's phone?
Not yet. They're still working on it.
We're gonna need that phone
and a little help from Wylie.
Is it possible to get the camp on lockdown...
No one in or out?
I might be able to claim the investigation
requires it for a couple of hours
- but no more than that.
- Plenty long enough.
Hey.
Morning. What's up?
- I need you to do something for me.
- Something shady for Jane?
- Why do you ask?
- Because people only talk to me like this
When we're doing
something shady for Jane.
I need you to create an electronic trail
that makes it look like the FBI just released
millions of dollars in frozen assets.
You mean a DNS hijacking?
When... when you go
to a bank's website
it redirects you to a phony version
of the same site.
You can make it look
like anything you want.
Yes... that. And yes, it's for Jane.
- Okay. Sure.
- You can do it?
- With my eyes closed.
- Good man.
- Got your message. What's up?
- I thought about your offer.
You want your assets
made available to you, right?
So you can take a little trip
before the trial starts?
The cost is 30%
of whatever funds I free up.
At this moment, I'm gonna ask...
are you wearing a wire?
No.
'Cause if you are and you lied just now,
this is entrapment.
30... that's the price.
20.
I am the only one
that can help you right now.
If you don't believe me,
ask Patrick Jane.
30.
All right.
Your funds are now set free,
minus my percentage.
Jim Matthews won't know
for at least three days.
- That's it?
- Check your account.
Nice doing business with you.
He just checked the website.
Everything looks good.
- Gryska bought it.
- Good.
- Okay.
- Mr. Jane.
- Any sign of Kilgallen?
- Afraid not.
Well, find him soon, please.
I'd very much like to fire him.
Sure. You, uh, look a little put off.
What seems to be the trouble?
Well, thanks to your FBI blockade
our speaker can't get into the camp.
We're gonna have to
postpone the talk.
Oh. I a... I am sorry. That is...
that is... that's very disappointing.
Yeah. People are
gonna be disappointed.
Well, you know,
I used to be a magician.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I was pretty good at it, actually.
I-I could try and entertain the troops
for you briefly
if you'd like, if you twisted my arm.
I mean, it's the least I could do
after all the trouble I've caused.
- Yeah, I'm not so sure about that.
- Just, this... is this yours?
I mean, I'd only charge you
like a dollar.
My God, that was incredible.
I guess the members might be interested
in... seeing something, yeah.
Oh, sure they would. I've got some props,
but I can take care of that.
We'll have some fun. Okay?
Put a smile on that face, huh?
See you later.
Okay, people.
Let's get together, shall we?
Thanks for coming.
- It's important nobody overhear us.
- Where were you?
- I was arranging to perform this afternoon.
- Why?
Just a minute.
Do you have Madison's phone?
Here.
The techs say that there's an audio file
recorded at 5:52 the morning
of Madison's murder.
Apparently, she recorded
a message for herself.
That was around
the same time she was killed.
What if she got audio
of the... of the killer?
- What's on it?
- They don't know. It's too damaged.
They can repair it,
but it'll take weeks.
- No need. We can identify the killer today.
- How?
I'm gonna do a routine onstage
with four objects
that I will say I got from the club's
lost and found.
One of those will be this phone.
When the killer sees it
he will identify it as Madison's.
And think that there's evidence on it.
Well, he doesn't know
that the FBI has it.
He's gonna think
it's in the lost and found.
And after the show, he will go to the
lost and found and try to take it back.
- That's when we get him.
- Nice.
- Unless he doesn't try to take it.
- Oh, he will.
It's like offering honey to a hungry bear.
He won't be able to resist.
Now I'm gonna place this card
back into the deck. Do a little dance.
And if you look in your right pant pocket
I think you might find...
What do you got in there?
How did you do that, Jim?
Thank you. Thank you.
Now please take a seat.
I'm gonna do one more thing for you.
I'm gonna need the assistance of the
irreplaceable special agent Teresa Lisbon.
Earlier today, I approached
four random members of the club.
Are they here?
Could you raise your hands?
Yes. I asked each of these men
to go to the club lost and found
and to choose one item
and place it in a cardboard box
and then seal that box.
- Do we have the box here?
- Yeah.
Thank you.
Now, just to be clear,
neither I nor agent Lisbon
saw what you picked
or know the contents of this box.
- Is that correct?
- That's correct.
Excellent.
Now, without the benefit of sight
I am going to attempt to identify each object
as agent Lisbon holds it up.
- Are we ready?
- Yep.
- Here's the box.
- Okay, no, not here.
- I have a chair back here.
- Okay, just over... Yeah, it's right here.
- You're doing good, Lisbon.
- Okay.
You're doing good.
Just stay calm. Relax.
Just let your beauty show.
- Okay, are we ready, agent Lisbon?
- Yes, we are.
Then let's begin!
First item.
What am I holding
in my hand?
It takes a licking
but keeps on ticking.
- A watch?
- Correct.
Next!
What am I holding
in my hand now?
They say it's mightier than the...
- is it a pen?
- Yes, it is.
Two for two.
What is in my hand now?
This one is difficult.
If I could only just...
See.
- Glasses?
- You are correct.
Last one.
- Can you figure this one out?
- It's a word.
"Harm." No.
"Hurt"? "Hurt"... no.
"Broken."
Broken...
Broken... Cell.
is it a broken cellphone?
Yes, it is.
Thank you!
Thank you. Really, thank you.
And... Thank you.
A big Foragers' thank you to Mr. Jane
and special agent Lisbon.
Terrific. Terrific.
Beautiful.
Good to see you.
How are you doing?
I know you can hear me...
And see me...
'cause you've got a camera in here.
You did it so you can blackmail
one of Madison's clients.
It's how you also knew
that you needed to clean that golf cart
"before the tech got here."
"We only talked about it in this room
so we know you heard."
It's how you also knew
not to take the phone.
"But I still got it."
And it still has evidence
that will implicate you.
And given the exchange
that I know you witnessed in here
between me and Mr. Gryska
I'm pretty sure that you know
that I am willing to make a deal.
"I'll give you 10 minutes."
What kind of deal
are we talking about?
None at all.
Go!
What are you d...
I didn't do anything!
Et voilà.
A honey bear.
We found Kilgallen's laptop
in your room, Mr. Dyer.
Your client Grant Kimura
had scheduled a session
to see Madison Pryce at 10:00
on the day she died.
You were gonna blackmail him,
weren't you?
There are some... irregularities
in grant's accounts.
I could explain everything.
But I needed some leverage.
When grant invited me...
To the Foragers' again
I thought about... The girl in cabin 9.
He'd been with her before.
So I cut a deal with Kilgallen.
- He let you put the camera in the cabin.
- For a fee.
Kilgallen always had his hand out.
But when I went to the cabin
to put the camera in that morning...
the girl came back early.
What are you doing?
"I went after her."
"I was just trying to...
Make her stop."
"And she just...
Stopped moving."
So, you left kimura's
golf-ball marker in there
- to throw suspicion on him.
- Yes.
I thought that if there was legal trouble
I could help him, he would be grateful
and he would forget
the financial stuff.
- Kilgallen figured out what had happened.
- Right away.
And he put his hand out...
Said that he'd be quiet if I paid.
And we met to settle the terms.
That thing with the phone
was a trick, wasn't it?
Oh, yes.
There's nothing on that phone.
And Gryska never got
any money, did he?
No. Gryska's under arrest...
just like you.
- I'm sorry we had to put this off.
- Oh, it's okay.
I took another girl out to dinner
last night instead.
- Really?
- Yeah.
You trying to make me jealous?
- What's her name?
- Gladys...
- E-eg-egbert.
- Gladys... Egbert? Hmm? Yeah?
That's the best I could do
on the spur of the moment.
You are a terrible liar.
I like that in a man.
Well, I'm glad.
I'm a lousy liar.
So you're right.
Actually, there's, uh, there's
something I wanted to tell you.
What?
That work stuff...
it's actually a promotion.
Really? What kind?
The bureau is forming a task force
to deal with international art theft.
It'll be working with Scotland yard
and other agencies.
Long story short...
they, uh... they... they...
they want me to run it.
Congratulations. That's fantastic.
Yeah, but they want me
to run it from D.C.
- So I'm telling them "no."
- You can't do that.
- I'm allowed.
- It's a great job, okay?
You can't turn it down.
I'm not a kid.
I've been married and divorced.
I know when something's real.
And when it could get serious.
I feel that way about us.
Do you... Feel that way?
Yeah, I do.
Look, one thing I know is that when
you feel that way about someone
you got to hang on, 'cause...
because it doesn't happen very often.
Marcus.
You cannot turn down this job.
They are not gonna offer it to you again.
I know.
- It's okay.
- No, it's not.
At the same time, the truth is,
I don't want you to go.
I really don't.
What if you came with me?
What?
I'm asking what if...
We went to D.C...
You and me, together?
What would you think
of that, Teresa?